{
    "subject": "resource/Alex_Troup",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Forfar",
    "human_readable": "Alex Troup was born in Forfar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8809868693351746,
            "question": "Where was Alex Troup born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7597384452819824,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Alex Troup and Forfar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6882844567298889,
            "question": "What is known about Alex Troup's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6554359793663025,
            "question": "Can you tell me the city of Alex Troup's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36577972769737244,
            "question": "Where might Alex Troup currently reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34515175223350525,
            "question": "Are there any notable individuals from Forfar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3296198546886444,
            "question": "Could you provide more details about Alex Troup?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32347753643989563,
            "question": "What else is known about Alex Troup?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2827005684375763,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of people born in Forfar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12252811342477798,
            "question": "Is Forfar a place in Scotland?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alex Troup was born in Forfar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3215_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common characteristics of people born in Forfar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3215_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What else is known about Alex Troup?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3215_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you provide more details about Alex Troup?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3215_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3215_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\n\n\"Alex Troup was born in Forfar.\"\n\nBased on the provided context information, specifically from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3215/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3215/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt, the information supports the triple. The documents mention that \"Born in Forfar\" for Alec Troup (the same person as Alex Troup) in both files.\n\nTherefore, the response is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Alexander (Alec) Troup was born in Forfar, Scotland."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}